{
    "subject": "resource/In_the_Heart_of_the_Country",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/South_Africa",
    "human_readable": "The country in which In the Heart of the Country is set is South Africa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9715438485145569,
            "question": "Is 'In the Heart of the Country' a story set in South Africa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.815761923789978,
            "question": "Is there a connection between South Africa and the story 'In the Heart of the Country'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5896255970001221,
            "question": "Where is the story 'In the Heart of the Country' set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49948686361312866,
            "question": "What country serves as the backdrop for 'In the Heart of the Country'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3304087519645691,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of the events in 'In the Heart of the Country'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31168973445892334,
            "question": "What can you infer about the characters in 'In the Heart of the Country' based on the setting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2986486554145813,
            "question": "Can you tell me the setting of the novel 'In the Heart of the Country'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25512558221817017,
            "question": "If you were to visit the setting of 'In the Heart of the Country', where would you go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21953561902046204,
            "question": "How does the setting of 'In the Heart of the Country' contribute to the overall theme of the story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15541768074035645,
            "question": "What kind of atmosphere might the setting of 'In the Heart of the Country' create for readers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The country in which In the Heart of the Country is set is South Africa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3903_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the setting of 'In the Heart of the Country' contribute to the overall theme of the story?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3903_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to visit the setting of 'In the Heart of the Country', where would you go?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3903_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the setting of the novel 'In the Heart of the Country'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3903_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_163.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3903_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as there are several mentions of South Africa being the primary filming location for the film \"Heart of the Hunter\", and also being the country where certain events or locations related to the film take place."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information supports that \"Heart of the Hunter\" was filmed in South Africa, and mentions various locations such as Cape Town City Hall and Swartberg Mountains within South Africa. Therefore, the statement that the country in which \"Heart of the Hunter\" is set is South Africa is correct based on the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}